<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Posts on weslack</title><link>/post/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on weslack</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>All content is free, unencumbered, and released into the public domain. Do with it what you want. &lt;a href="https://weslack.team/LICENSE.txt">Unlicense&lt;/a></copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 00:31:28 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mosquitto Flag 2</title><link>/post/mosquitto-2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 09:41:43 -0700</pubDate><guid>/post/mosquitto-2/</guid><description>Challenge See if you have the patience to scratch the itch; patience is key. Mosquitto bites are so annoying! Except, in this case.. you can become an admin. Connect at: x.x.x.x:1883 using iot:iot Web Portal: http://x.x.x.x
Solve Look at the new Mosquitto server, connecting using the following command
mosquitto_sub -h x.x.x.x -p 1883 -u iot -P iot -t &amp;#34;#&amp;#34; Grab the text that looks like a flag.
Base64 decode the username and password.</description></item><item><title>Black Box 1 Flag Writeup</title><link>/post/black-box-1-flag/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 13:29:43 -0700</pubDate><guid>/post/black-box-1-flag/</guid><description>Previous Exploit Doing a search of Control 4 C4-HC250-BL + exploit in Google netted us with the default password used to exploit. http://www.davidsonfamily.ca/discussion-board/topic/logging-into-controller/
Black Box 1 Flag I noticed there was a Black Box Challenge for Control 4, which we previously exploited.
With the password we previously used, we could ssh into the ip to access the directory: /etc/init.d/c4server.
We took the MD5 sum of /etc/init.d/c4server to retrieve the flag.</description></item><item><title>Control4 Flag</title><link>/post/control4-flag/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 13:22:15 -0700</pubDate><guid>/post/control4-flag/</guid><description>After doing some research on the control4 product, we found that there is a default root password.
user password root t0talc0ntr0l4! Getting the flag The flag is located on the SD card, so we go look in /mnt/sd/
$ cd /mnt/sd/ $ ls Flag.txt flash lost+found We found the flag, and now we can cat it out and capture it.</description></item><item><title>Setting Up and Using Tools</title><link>/post/setting-up-and-using-tools/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 12:18:30 -0700</pubDate><guid>/post/setting-up-and-using-tools/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve learned how to use couple different tools since we&amp;rsquo;ve started working on the SOHOplessly Broken CTF.
Kali We set up a Vagrant machine to use as a common starting place for each of our machines. It has all of the standard Kali tools installed, as well as some other standard exploit tools.
Requirements Git Vagrant Virtualbox Package Managers It is recommended to use a package manager for installing and updating this software.</description></item><item><title>Day2 Port Scan Update</title><link>/post/day2-port-scan-update/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 12:16:14 -0700</pubDate><guid>/post/day2-port-scan-update/</guid><description>After getting connected to the SOHOplesslyBroken VPN, we did an nmap scan of the local IP range for any devices. This as an update to show what flags have already been captured.
nmap 192.168.10.0/24 Control4 Open Source Software Notice url: http://192.168.10.101/
PORT STATE SERVICE 21/tcp closed ftp 22/tcp closed ssh 80/tcp open http Current State: Has not been accessed.</description></item><item><title>Mosquitto Flag</title><link>/post/mosquitto-flag/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 11:19:07 -0700</pubDate><guid>/post/mosquitto-flag/</guid><description>The hint for the flag was.
See if you have the patience to scratch the itch; patience is key. Mosquitto bites are so annoying! Connect at: 209.97.159.20:1883 Creds: iot:iot
We had a feeling that this had something to do with MQTT based off the mosquitto name. Searching for port 1883 confirmed this, as this is a standard port of MQTT.
We installed the mosquitto client using:
sudo apt install -y mosquitto-clients We then connected to the server using:</description></item><item><title>Fortinet Flag</title><link>/post/fortinet-flag/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2020 23:33:58 -0700</pubDate><guid>/post/fortinet-flag/</guid><description>Finding the exploit, we did some google-fu and learned a bit about some of the exploits for the device, but we didn&amp;rsquo;t know which device on the network it was.
We connected to one of the devices and figured out that the favicon of the admin page was Fortinet&amp;rsquo;s logo. From there we started to run some of the exploits. The one that worked for us was https://www.exploit-db.com/exploits/43386
Exploit #!/usr/bin/env python # SSH Backdoor for FortiGate OS Version 4.</description></item><item><title>GeoVision Flag</title><link>/post/geovision-flag/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2020 23:33:44 -0700</pubDate><guid>/post/geovision-flag/</guid><description>Doing a search of GeoVision GV-SNVR0811 + exploit in Google netted us with a ton of results with the following exploit.
https://www.exploit-db.com/exploits/45065
Exploit # Exploit Title: GeoVision GV-SNVR0811 Directory Traversal # Exploit Author: Berk Dusunur # Google Dork: N/A # Type: Hardware # Date: 2018-07-21 # Vendor Homepage: http://www.geovision.com.tw/product/GV-SNVR0811 # Software Link: http://www.geovision.com.tw/product/GV-SNVR0811 # Affected Version: N/A # Tested on: Parrot OS # CVE : N/A # Proof Of Concept GET Request GET .</description></item><item><title>Nuuo NVR Mini Flag</title><link>/post/nuuo-flag/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2020 14:02:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>/post/nuuo-flag/</guid><description>We were able to get the flag off of our first device using a known exploit. We found this known exploit by searching for the device + exploit in to Google. We found the following vulnerability in Exploit Database.
https://www.exploit-db.com/exploits/40209
Script #!/usr/bin/env python # # # NUUO Remote Root Exploit # # # Vendor: NUUO Inc. # Product web page: http://www.nuuo.com # Affected version: &amp;lt;=3.0.8 # # Summary: NUUO NVRmini 2 is the lightweight, portable NVR solution with NAS # functionality.</description></item><item><title>Initial Port Scan</title><link>/post/initial-port-scan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2020 12:34:02 -0700</pubDate><guid>/post/initial-port-scan/</guid><description>After getting connected to the SOHOplesslyBroken VPN, we did an nmap scan of the local IP range for any devices.
nmap 192.168.10.0/24 Control4 Open Source Software Notice url: http://192.168.10.101/
PORT STATE SERVICE 21/tcp closed ftp 22/tcp closed ssh 80/tcp open http Link Clicker url: http://192.168.10.187/
PORT STATE SERVICE 80/tcp open http NUUO Network Video Recorder url: http://192.</description></item><item><title>Website</title><link>/post/website/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 13:11:07 -0700</pubDate><guid>/post/website/</guid><description>&lt;p>The point of this website is to keep track of our captured flags and the things we&amp;rsquo;ve learned at &lt;a href="https://defcon.org"target="_blank">defcon28&lt;/a>.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>